Samitown
Hello everyone! We, Natagaarumi here!
Today, who knows more about Nanaka Tomita!
I would like to decide who is Tomita!
I've been working on this image for quite a long time.
Honda is me, Moe Tanizawa
Nagata is Miyuki Honda
Suganami and Suzuki are Ogi.
And Kawaguchi is Momo-chan.
And Momo for Kawaguchi.
Well, let's all work hard to become Tomita!
Only for you!
I see.
Well then, let's go to the first question! Here is the first question!
Ugh! Who do you respect?
About this much! Wow!
I don't think I've heard of many people like that. It might be difficult.
Wow. You're right.
Wow, you're right, the O series is full of people who think about other people.
I don't know.
Who do you admire?
Yes. Did you write it?
Yes, I said it.
So, now that everyone has written their names, I'd like to announce them.
Who do you respect?
Boom! Dong!
Oh! What?
Aah! Aah!
Mother... Tachibana-san... Mother...
Aaah! Wait!
Oh! Whoa! Whoa! Whoo!
Oh, yeah! Hey! I know, right?
Yeah, that's what I thought. That's what bothered me.
You know, that gut feeling, the first thing that came to me, the first thing that came to me.
Yes, I drew the character's face.
I'd like to see the correct answer. Here it is!
Who do you admire?
Who do you admire? Who do you admire?
Well...
My high school teacher.
Aaaaah!
Oh, my God!
Oh, because I've heard of him!
Well, why then?
I just thought of it!
Why?
We all respect you, really.
It changes from day to day.
I see... I see...
So, no one got the first question right.
Let's continue.
What do you like about Kagoshima?
There are so many!
What? There are so many!
Yes, there are!
One, right!
One! One?
One?
One!
That's great ASMR.
I heard that!
I wonder what it is?
Okay, so what's good about Kagoshima?
Seino!
Ta-da!
Chicken sashimi is delicious!
Kagoshima! White bear!
Oh!
It's all over the place!
It's a good place for everyone!
Everyone is nice!
It's like Kagoshima. Like when you think of Kagoshima.
Certainly the one I, you know, none of them, you know, the one I say a lot.
That's right.
Well then, let's see the correct answers right away!
Good points of Kagoshima!
Good things about Kagoshima! Sakurajima is there!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
So, Saya got it right!
I'm so happy!
Sad!
Really?
Just a little lead.
Sad!
But you know, when I get asked by fans what I recommend at online events and such, I always say the one I'm putting out. I've been asking them what they'd like to see in an online event.
Really?
All of them.
You mean you missed it?
It's so close!
It means a lot of good things!
Why are you so creepy!
So, Saya is in the lead!
Yay!
Next is the third question! Please!
What does not equal me mean to Tominanaka?
Oh!
This is fun!
I'm torn between two.
No, I'm torn between two.
Two and what?
I'm torn between two.
What? Wait a minute. I'm going with this one.
You want to go this way?
Yeah!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, okay.
Yes!
What was that? What was that?
Two!
What does not equal me mean to Tominanaka?
Se-no!
Four!
Oh!
Youth!
A place where you can meet a different you
Oh!
Farewell for sure.
Yes, yes, yes.
So, I would like to see the correct answer! Please do!
What is Not Equal Me?
My Life
Sumida Bono Bike
Sumida Bono I thought everyone would write that
Sumida creator Green Beard Yada!
green I can hear the taste of green now
Sumida Bono The taste green is different
Sumida Bono I didn't quite hear the flavor green, empty.
I'll write it that way next time.
Here you go.
And now the fourth one, please.
You have seven days to compose an AYUEO essay.
Wow, that's interesting.
It's really momentum.
I see.
Go for it, guys.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
I did it.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
one, two, three, four...
Down.
Here we go
Next, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
I wanna cry my heart out
I wanna go cry my eyes out
No, no, no
Something-chan really wants to go to Kagoshima
Oh!
She's trying to make a pooh-pooh.
I like it.
It's perfect.
Next, something, something, something, Tomica, something...
Something... something...
What is it?
what?
what
Oh!
Nice Despite
something
Chamichan...
What is it?
something
Like the wind
It's like the wind, isn't it?
Oh, wow!
Exquisite judgment.
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, guys, I got a little graze. Look.
What about you, something-chan?
What's wrong with you? What's wrong with you?
Don't hide, don't hide, don't hide.
Cover your eyes.
Like this.
You're right about the stretchy stick.
It's just a matter of how you say it.
Half a present
Is that okay?
I want to go to Kagoshima.
Oh, oh, oh, oh...
I'm very kind.
0.2 points.
Sayu is leading.
1.2 points.
Okay, then, continuing.
Fifth question.
What would you say if someone told you that you are a very beautiful woman today?
Ah...
What would I say?
Oh, wow.
That's amazing.
I saw something.
Oh, wow.
You're so confident.
But listen, you've been acting all confident since the beginning, haven't you?
Ha-ha-ha.
Yes, I did.
Oh, I got it.
Yes, I got it.
You're looking very beautiful today, aren't you?
I recently got a haircut.
Ah...
That's for sure.
I'll go.
You're so beautiful today.
I don't know about that, but it leaked today.
Uh-oh. Ahh.
Sure thing.
Okay, I'll go last.
You're really beautiful today, aren't you?
Oh, wow.
Thank you very much.
I'm worried about the little one.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's all there.
It's true.
It's possible.
I'd like to see the answers, please.
Yes.
I'm just happy.
I say that sometimes.
I'm just frustrated.
Let's see your score, Kentan.
Yes, I got 0.5 points
And Sayachan got 1.2.
Yay!
Kirari Ochiai got 0 points.
Ah...
How many questions are left?
Ta-da!
Then you can make up for it.
Next question, please.
What was your first impression of Kirari Ochiai?
Oh!
Kirari.
Have we ever talked about this before?
Uh...
Yes, I have.
Oh, no, no, no, no... Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
Five years ago.
Five years ago... that's a very impressive meeting.
You're right.
We first had dinner together at Artition.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, I see.
What?
Write it down yourself.
I'm just gonna take it off.
Don't do that.
Oh, God.
I'll keep it simple.
I mean that as a compliment, Kirari.
Thank you.
I wrote it.
Let's start with mine and Saya-chan's answers.
Ta-da!
So tiny and cute!
Oh, wow!
She's so sparkly!
What should I say?
I can say...
It's like, “He's got a name.
I see.
So, Kirari.
She'll catch your eye.
Easy to talk to.
Uh...
That's not an ah.
Not that one.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll look at it next time.
Ehhhh...
Tiny.
Tiny and cute.
Amazing. It's amazing.
I heard the photography show Meguro drainkor a d and iię
I congratulate you on the pattiras that is angry with chess!
So today, please give me a SAYANA UBUKU!
영文
Buber ely ni
me
C'mon tours
Cheerfully pyoon
Cute
Nice song.
Your ears are so tight
Saya-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa-usa
Jump, jump, saya-usa-usa-usa-usa
Let's go next.
Okay, I'll go.
Saya, sayasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasasas.
I want to continue.
I'm not going to continue...
How's it going?
How do you like it?
I think it's him.
Oh...
I'll take it then.
I did it.
It's fun.
You're going up at the end, isn't that fun?
Let's hurry up and get it right.
Then I'd like to see the correct answers.
Please do.
I'm stumped!
Wait a minute.
Saya's song?
Ya... Ya... Ya... Ya...
Yes! It's Saya!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's better this way. It's better to go up this way.
I really do.
I don't care if you come out...
Ya!
We're all saying, “This is it!
That's great.
You guys are so talented.
Thank you.
Last one?
The last one.
Last?
Uh...
What's the score?
I'm telling you!
No!
Hey!
But you know what?
It's a variety show.
So...
The last one is putty!
Chance for full bloom.
Can you do it?
Saya's triplets.
Oh, my God!
Why is it so long?
Last question, please.
Oh!
You're too cute about Moeiko Misawa.
What kind of place is that?
I don't want to write it myself!
I don't like it!
It's a three-ring series.
I wasn't supposed to write it.
Did you get it? Yes, I did.
Okay, you go first.
You two, go ahead. I'll have two people present.
I'd like to make a final presentation.
Se-no!
Aah!
I'm going to put my catch on my clothes.
Pokko pokko.
That's why...
I'm a chatty one.
Hmm.
I'm torn.
Well, you, too.
Let's go!
Kanji for “moeko”.
What's that?
I'll tell you...
I like her name.
I like it.
It's a cute kanji.
I'm pretty sure that's not it.
Then give me the correct answer.
I'll take the correct one.
This place is too cute.
He's so proud of himself.
You know, when he's got a gag or something.
You know, like a gag or something.
I couldn't catch it.
I said, “Hmm? I said, “What?
He got really pissed off.
And then...
And then he'd come back and...
I wonder if he'll come back and try again.
Cute!
It's not cute.
What a rakugo
Karakura.
I thought it was a little regrettable.
That's right... because, you know...
That's what's mischievous. That's what mischievousness is all about.
Three points
Ahhh...
Aaaaaaahhhh...
Yes, I did.
So, the results are in!
win, win, win, win!
Kirarin
hand down
me
0.5 points
and
TAYASU-chan
5.2 points
That's not even close.
Tanizaki-san wins!
Yay!
I'm so happy, so happy!
It was too overwhelming!
I'm so disappointed!
So it was a very close game, King Tomita!
No, not at all.
Not at all!
But it was so much fun!
It was fun!
Oh, it was fun!
Well, that's all for now, King Tomita!
Bye-bye!
Oh, that was fun.